Guide to the Frank Logue Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Frank Logue papers
1974-1979
MS 1178
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
41
(41 boxes)
The papers consists of subject files, which include correspondence, maintained by Logue and his staff during his tenure as mayor of New Haven, Connecticut.
Logue, Francis Fay
Scope and Contents
The papers consists of subject files, which include correspondence, maintained by Logue and his staff during his tenure as mayor of New Haven, Connecticut.
Biographical / Historical
Frank Logue was born in Philadelphia on August 18, 1924. He attended Yale University, enlisted in the military after Pearl Harbor, and served as an infantry soldier in France. He returned to Yale Law School in 1948. Logue entered politics in 1953 and held a number of positions, serving on the New Haven Board of Aldermen from 1972-1975. He was mayor of New Haven from 1976 to 1979. Logue died in Hamden, Connecticut, on December 31, 2010.
Conditions Governing Access
The material is unprocessed and may contain sensitive information or be in a physical state that would prohibit use. Researchers wishing to request access should email mssa.assist@yale.edu requesting specific box numbers in order to initiate the review process, which may take several weeks.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Deposited by Frank Logue in 1979, gifted to Yale University in 1995.
General
Boxes 7-12, 19-24, and 31-36 were flood damaged. Reference archivists/researchers should be aware that some of the material in the flood damaged boxes does not correspond exactly to the folder listing, although most of it does. Particularly, folders which were listed in the original inventory as being in box 24, from "Bank - Connecticut Savings" to "Commissions - New Haven Green" are missing and were subsequently deleted from the inventory.
New Haven (Conn.); New Haven (Conn.) -- Appropriations and expenditures; City planning -- Connecticut -- New Haven; New Haven (Conn.) -- Economic conditions; Mayors -- Connecticut -- New Haven; Logue, Francis Fay
- Affirmative Action (Box 1)
- Airport (Box 1)
- Airport (Box 1)
- Airport regarding correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
- Airport regarding correspondence, 1977 (Box 1)
- Airport regarding correspondence, 1978 (Box 1)
- Airport regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 1)
- Airport regarding reports/annual report (Box 1)
- Airport regarding reports/Blaine contract (Box 1)
- Airport regarding reports/master plan (Box 1)
- Allegheny-Airlines-Ransome (Box 1)
- Civil Aeronautics Board-Airlines (Box 1)
- Airlines-Civil Aeronautics Board (Box 1)
- Airport manager (Box 1)
- Airport manager (Box 1)
- Airports-Tweed New Haven resumes (Box 1)
- Alderman, Board of (Box 1)
- Assessor (Box 1)
- City Assessor (resumes), 1979 (Box 1)
- Assessments (Box 1)
- Reassessments (Box 1)
- Building (Box 1)
- Building department (Box 1)
- Capital projects, 1979 (Box 1)
- Charter revision (Box 1)
- Chief Administrative Officer (Box 1)
- Chief Administrative Officer (2) (Box 1)
- Chief Administrative Officer-city buildings (Box 1)
- Chief Administrative Officer-fuel audit (Box 1)
- Chief Administrative Officer (CAO)-management review (Box 1)
- Chief Administrative Officer (CAO)-management information system (Box 1)
- Vehicle use policy (Box 1)
- City hall (Box 1)
- City engineer (Box 1)
- City engineer, 1979 (Box 1)
- City engineer (Box 1)
- City engineer (Box 2)
- City plan (Box 2)
- City Plan Commission, 1979 (Box 2)
- City Plan (Box 2)
- City Plan-Comprehensive Housing Task Force (Box 2)
- City-Town clerk (1) (Box 2)
- Civil defense (Box 2)
- Civil defense, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
- Civil defense, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
- Civil defense-annual report (Box 2)
- Civil defense-emergency operations plan (Box 2)
- Civil service office
  - Civil Service Office (Box 2)
  - Personnel and civil service-MGMT pay plan (Box 2)
  - Civil service-personnel (Box 2)
  - Personnel and civil service: Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA) (Box 2)
  - Civil service-commission (Box 2)
  - Civil service (Box 2)
  - Complaints (Box 2)
  - Complaints (Box 2)
  - Interviews-complaint clerk (Box 2)
- Coliseum (Box 2)
- Coliseum (Box 2)
- Coliseum-finance (Box 2)
- Coliseum-authority (Box 2)
- Coliseum (Box 2)
- Coliseum manager (Box 2)
- Coliseum-by-laws (Box 2)
- Coliseum-insurance (Box 2)
- Coliseum-parking garage (Box 2)
- Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) (1) (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA), 1974-1977 (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA)-Public Service Employment (PSE) (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA)-Parent Aide Program, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) correspondence, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) correspondence, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) (2) (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) Consortium (Box 2)
  - Consortium Mayoral Board (Box 2)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA)-Health, Education, and Welfare (HEW) (Box 2)
  - Central Counseling Unit (Box 3)
  - Central Job Development (Box 3)
  - Day Care Unit (Box 3)
  - Follow-up Unit (Box 3)
  - Unit-Health Services (Box 3)
  - Homemakers Program (Box 3)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA)-Manpower (Box 3)
  - Manpower-correspondence (Box 3)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA)-Area Manpower Planning Council (Box 3)
  - Occupational Instructors (Box 3)
  - CIC (Box 3)
  - Older Workers Unit (Box 3)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) personnel (Box 3)
  - Planning Unit (Box 3)
  - Public Services Unit (Box 3)
  - Skill Center Unit (Box 3)
  - Skill Center-correspondence (Box 3)
  - Summer Program-arts (Box 3)
  - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA)-Summer Youth Employment Program (Box 3)
  - Summer Youth Employment Program-correspondence (Box 3)
  - Title I (Box 3)
  - Title II (Box 3)
  - Title III (Box 3)
  - Title VI (Box 3)
  - Title VII (Box 3)
  - Title X (Box 3)
  - Title XIX (Box 3)
- Controller
  - Controller (Box 3)
  - Controller budget, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Controller budget, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
  - Controller budget, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Controller budget, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
  - Controller's office regarding Finance, Board of meetings, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Controller's office regarding Personnel Committee General Fund, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Controller's office regarding Personnel Committee General Fund, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Controller's office regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Bond application notes (Box 3)
  - Controller (1) (Box 3)
  - City budget-bargaining unit (Box 3)
  - Controller-vacation balances (Box 3)
  - Labor-workmen's compensation (Box 3)
  - Vouchers, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Controller-financial statements (Box 3)
  - Controller (2) (Box 3)
  - Controller-payroll, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Controller-payroll, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Controller-payroll, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Controller-payroll, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Controller audit-CDA (Box 3)
  - Controller General (Box 3)
  - Controller-education budget requests (Box 4)
  - Controller-human resources budget requests (Box 4)
  - Controller-budget (Box 4)
  - Controller-revenue (Box 4)
  - Controller-economic forecast (Box 4)
- Corporation Counsel
  - Corporation Counsel (Box 4)
  - Corporation Counsel (1), 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Corporation Counsel (2), 1977-1979 (Box 4)
  - Litigation-Avallone (Box 4)
  - Litigation-Celantano (Box 4)
  - Corporation Counsel-attorneys (Box 4)
- Cultural affairs
  - Cultural affairs (Box 4)
  - Cultural affairs (Box 4)
  - Cultural affairs-summer cabaret (Box 4)
- Department heads (Box 4)
- Department heads (Box 4)
- Development
  - Development (Box 4)
  - Development-FUSCO (Box 4)
  - Development-Newhallville Convalescent (Box 4)
  - Adult day care (Box 4)
  - Development-Pond Lily (Box 4)
  - Development-Pardee Sea Wall (Box 4)
  - Development administrator (Box 4)
  - Development (Box 4)
  - Development-Ninth Square (Box 4)
  - Gateway Landing Development (Box 4)
  - Distressed Cities Development (Box 4)
  - Development Commission
    - Development Commission, New Haven (Box 4)
    - Development Commission, New Haven, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
    - New Haven Development Commission, 1976 (Box 4)
    - New Haven Development Commission (3), 1977-1978 (Box 4)
    - Development-Commission's Corporation, 1979 (Box 4)
- Community Development
  - Community development (Box 5)
  - Community development-general (Box 5)
  - Community development-round table (Box 5)
  - Community development-I (Box 5)
  - Community development (I) (Box 5)
  - Community development-II (Box 5)
  - Community development-II Jan-Mar (Box 5)
  - Community development-II, 1976 April-December (Box 5)
  - Community development-II, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Community Development Association (CDA) II-National Veterans Fraternity (Box 5)
  - Community Development Association (CDA) II, III and IV Neighborhood Preservation Program (Box 5)
  - Community Development II-IV (Box 5)
  - Community Development III, IV (Box 6)
  - Community Development III, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Community Development III, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Community Development I, II, and III (Box 6)
  - Community Development IV (Box 6)
  - Community Development I, II, III, and IV (Box 6)
  - Community Development regarding financial statement, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Community Development IV, V, and VI (Box 6)
  - Community Development-first year program balance sheet and cost report (Box 6)
  - Community Development-second year program balance sheet and cost report (Box 6)
  - Community Development-third year program balance sheet and cost report (Box 6)
  - Community Development-fourth year program balance sheet and cost report (Box 6)
  - Community Development-fourth year status report: public service activities (Box 6)
  - Community Development-first year status report: summary of activities, 6/30/1978 (Box 6)
  - Community Development-second year status report: summary of activities, 6/30/1978 (Box 6)
  - Community Development-third year status report: summary of activities, 6/30/1978 (Box 6)
  - Community Development Title XX Social Services Plan (Box 6)
- Economic development
  - Economic development (1) (Box 6)
  - General economic development, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Economic development (4) (Box 6)
  - Overall Economic Development Program (OEDP) (1), 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Overall Economic Development Program (OEDP), 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Economic Development (2) (Box 6)
  - Economic Development (2), 1976 (Box 6)
  - Economic Development (1), correspondence, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Economic Development (3) (Box 6)
  - Economic Development (3), 1977 (Box 6)
  - Economic Development, 1978-1979 (Box 6)
  - Research objectives (Box 7)
  - Research approach (Box 7)
  - Findings in detail (Box 7)
  - Strategy formulation recommendations (Box 7)
  - Appendixes (Box 7)
  - Chamber of Commerce data (Box 7)
  - Economic development profile (Box 7)
  - Industrial park (Box 7)
  - Industrial financing (Box 7)
  - Redevelopment
    - Redevelopment-research (Box 7)
    - Redevelopment homesteading (Box 7)
    - Redevelopment-Taft-Adams (Box 7)
    - Redevelopment-Amtote (Box 7)
  - Economic development (NH) regarding Neighborhood Commercial Revitaliation Program, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Economic Development Task Force (Box 7)
  - Council for Urban Economic Development (CUED) (Box 7)
- Board of Education
  - Board of Education meetings-agenda, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Board of Education, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
- Education
  - Education-School Administrators Association (Box 7)
  - Education-bilingual (Box 7)
  - Education-breakfast program (Box 7)
  - Urban superintendants (Box 7)
  - Education-Title VII interim reports (Box 7)
  - Education (5) (Box 7)
  - Education Task force (Box 7)
  - Education-Head Start Policy Council (Box 7)
  - Education-school finance formula (Box 7)
  - Education-summer lunch program (Box 7)
  - Education-primary energy study (Box 7)
  - Education-report on schools (Box 7)
  - Education, special (Box 7)
  - Title X (Box 7)
  - Education (5) (Box 7)
  - Education (Box 7)
  - Betty Phillips (Box 7)
  - Betty Phillips (Box 7)
  - Political union (Box 7)
  - Public relations (Box 7)
  - Read seminar (Box 7)
  - Religion/church (Box 7)
  - Renovation and furniture (furnishings) (Box 7)
  - Residential facilities (Box 7)
  - Education (1) (Box 7)
  - Education (3) (Box 7)
  - Education-budget (Box 7)
  - Education-consortium (Box 7)
  - Education-administrator's manual (Box 7)
  - Education-equipment (Box 7)
  - Education-guidance (Box 7)
  - Education-ESAA project pilot (Box 8)
  - Education, board (Box 8)
  - Education, board-budget (Box 8)
  - Education, board-contract agreement (Box 8)
  - Education-capital improvements (Box 8)
  - Education-capital improvements projects, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
  - Education-summer studies program (Box 8)
  - Education-Parents Teachers Association (PTA) of New Haven (Box 8)
  - Education-food study service (Box 8)
  - Education, Board (1) (Box 8)
  - Education, Board-budget (Box 8)
  - Education, Board, 1976 March (Box 8)
  - Education, Board (2) (Box 8)
  - Education-gifted and talented programming (Box 8)
  - Education Board (3) (Box 8)
  - Education-Barbarito (Box 8)
  - Education-Betelman (Box 8)
  - Education, Board of Teachers (Box 8)
  - Education-superintendent (Box 8)
  - Education-Wexler (Box 8)
  - Education-Board-Balay, Harriet (Box 8)
  - Education-Board (4) (Box 8)
  - Q (Box 8)
  - R (Box 8)
  - Richter, Misha (Box 8)
  - Ludwig Rosenthal's Antiquariat (Box 8)
  - Education Board (6) (Box 8)
  - Education Board-general (Box 8)
  - Education Board (7) (Box 8)
  - Board of Education-bilingual Title VII-Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA) (Box 8)
  - Schools-athletics (Box 8)
  - Board of Education-school closings (Box 8)
  - Education, Board of-school crossing guards (Box 8)
  - Board of Education (Box 8)
  - Board of Education budget (Box 8)
  - Board of Education-cafeteria workers (Box 8)
  - Board of Education-Equal Education Opportunity Grant (Box 8)
  - Education, Board (8) (Box 8)
  - Board of Education (Box 8)
  - Education-parent participation (Box 8)
  - Board of Education-budget projection, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Education, Board-driver education (Box 8)
  - School custodians assignments (Box 8)
  - Education, Board of School Finance (Box 8)
  - Education, Board of-Iowa Basic Achievement Tests (Box 8)
  - Education, Board of-music program (Box 8)
  - Education, Board of-paraprofessional information (Box 8)
  - Education, Board-security (Box 8)
  - Schools
    - Education-schools (1) (Box 9)
    - Schools-New Haven Public-general (Box 9)
    - School, Baldwin (Box 9)
    - School, Beecher (Box 9)
    - School, Benhaven (Box 9)
    - Bishop Woods School (Box 9)
    - School, Celantano (Box 9)
    - School-St. Brendan's Parochial (Box 9)
    - School, Cheever (Box 9)
    - School, Conte Senior (Box 9)
    - School, Davis (Box 9)
    - School, Derryfield (Box 9)
    - School, Dixwell (Box 9)
    - School, Dwight (Box 9)
    - School, East Rock Community (Box 9)
    - Education-Schools (2) (Box 9)
    - School, Edgewood (Box 9)
    - School, Edwards (Box 9)
    - School, Fair Haven Middle (Box 9)
    - Helene Grant School (Box 9)
    - School, Hill Middle (Box 9)
    - Education-Schools (Box 9)
    - High Schools-Hillhouse (Box 9)
    - Jackie Robinson Middle (Box 9)
    - High Schools-Lee (Box 9)
    - Lee Annex (Box 9)
    - Schools, Martin Luther King (Box 9)
    - Schools, Newhallville (Box 9)
    - School-Roberto Clemente (Box 9)
    - School, Scranton (Box 9)
    - Schools-Sheriden Middle School (Box 9)
    - School, Troup Middle (Box 9)
    - School, Truman (Box 9)
    - School, Welch Annex (Box 9)
    - School, Winchester Community (Box 9)
    - High Schools-Wilbur Cross (Box 9)
    - School, Woodward Street (Box 9)
    - School, Worthington Hooker (Box 9)
    - Schools-community councils (Box 9)
    - Neighborhood Afterschool Coop (Box 9)
    - Schools-vision screening (Box 9)
    - Education, Board of-school violence (Box 9)
    - High school coaches (Box 9)
    - School crossing guards (Box 9)
- Equal Opportunities Commission (Box 9)
- Equal Opportunities Commission (Box 9)
- Fair housing (Box 9)
- Ethics, board (Box 9)
- Ethics-board (Box 9)
- Fair employment (Box 9)
- Fair employment plan executive order, 1976 July 9 (Box 9)
- Fair employment officer (Box 9)
- Fair Rent Commission (Box 9)
- Fair housing (Box 9)
- Fair Rent Commission (Box 9)
- Finance, Board
  - Finance, Board (1) (Box 9)
  - Finance, Board, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 January 8 (Box 9)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 January 15-21 (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board (2) (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 January (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 February (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1970 March (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 April (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board (3) (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 May (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 June (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 July (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 August-September (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1976 October-November (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board (4) (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1977 January (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1977 July-September (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1977 October-December (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board (5) (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1978 January (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1978 February-March (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board of (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board, 1978 April-May (Box 10)
  - Finance, Board of regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 10)
- Fire Department
  - Fire Department (Box 10)
  - Fire Commissioners-Board, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Fire Commissioners Board (Box 10)
  - Fire Department-annual reports (Box 10)
  - Fire Department-employment (Box 10)
  - Fire Department-fire hydrants (Box 10)
  - Fire Department-fire marshall (Box 10)
  - Fire Department regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Fire Department-arson squad (Box 10)
  - Fire Department regarding Board of Fire Commissioner, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Fire Department regarding Janet Ingallo #5 (Box 10)
  - Fire Department-general (Box 10)
  - Fire Department (2) (Box 11)
  - Fire Department (Box 11)
  - Fire Department-Chief (Box 11)
  - Fire Service (Box 11)
  - Fire pensions (Box 11)
  - Reorganization-Fire Department (Box 11)
- Health Department
  - Health, Board (Box 11)
  - Health Department (Box 11)
  - Health Dept. (Box 11)
  - Health Department (2) (Box 11)
  - Health Department (3) (Box 11)
  - Health Department (4) (Box 11)
  - Communicty Health Care Plan (CHCP) (Box 11)
  - Hill Health Center (Box 11)
  - South Central Comprehensive Health Planning (SCC) (Box 11)
  - Health (Box 11)
  - Health department (Box 11)
  - Health department-director (Box 11)
  - Health department-lead paint poisoning (Box 11)
  - Health department-mental health (Box 11)
  - Health-task force (Box 11)
- Animal shelter (Box 11)
- Animal shelter (Box 11)
- Housing authority
  - Housing authority (1) (Box 11)
  - Housing authority, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Housing authority-police department (Box 11)
  - Housing authority (2) (Box 11)
  - Housing authority-Farnham, Connecticut (Box 11)
  - Housing legislation (Box 11)
  - Housing Authority-McQueeney (Box 11)
  - Housing Authority-Park Ridge Towers (Box 11)
  - Housing Authority-Ruopollo Mano (Box 11)
  - Housing Authority (3) (Box 11)
  - Housing Authority (1), 1976-1977 (Box 11)
  - Housing Authority (3), 1978 (Box 11)
  - Housing Authority (4) (Box 12)
  - Housing Authority Director (Box 12)
  - Housing Authority (2) (Box 12)
  - Housing Authority (4), 1979 (Box 12)
  - Housing Authority-utility bills (Box 12)
  - Housing Authority's security (Box 12)
  - Housing Authority: subsidy and energy conservation bill (Box 12)
  - Housing Authority-Tenants Representative Council (Box 12)
- Human Resources
  - Human resources (Box 12)
  - Human resources (Box 12)
  - HRS-Easter Seals Goodwill Industries rehabilitation (Box 12)
  - Human services (Box 12)
  - Human resources (1) (Box 12)
  - Human resources regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Human Resources, Department of (Box 12)
  - Human Resources, Department of (Box 12)
  - Human Resources Director (Box 12)
  - Human Resources (3) (Box 12)
  - Elderly (Box 12)
  - Human Services Department regarding elderly services, proposed reorganization, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Elderly (2) (Box 12)
  - HRA-Elderly (Box 12)
  - HRA-O.I.C.-Urban problems (Box 12)
  - West Haven Day Care Center (Box 12)
  - HRA reorganization (Box 12)
  - HRA-elderly-nutrition (Box 12)
  - Human resources (2) (Box 12)
  - HRA-special attention HEW (Box 12)
  - HRA-Baltimore Project (Box 12)
  - Police department (4) (Box 12)
  - Police-gun control (Box 12)
  - Police-Mongillo, Insler and Jones (Box 12)
  - Police-research reports (Box 12)
  - Police-silver shields (Box 12)
  - Police and Firemen's Retirement Board (Box 12)
  - HRA elderly-Casa Otonal (Box 13)
  - HRA elderly, Hispanic (Box 13)
  - HRA-senior citizens center (Box 13)
  - HRA-rehabilitation center (Box 13)
  - HRA-day care (Box 13)
  - Senior citizen's-lighthouse (Box 13)
  - HRA-Bella Vista: Carabetta (Box 13)
  - Handicapped services, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Handicapped transportation plan (Box 13)
  - HRA-handicapped (Box 13)
  - HRA-handicapped services (Box 13)
  - Human resources (3) (Box 13)
  - HRA-youth (Box 13)
  - HRA-drugs (Box 13)
  - HRA-fuel bank for needy (Box 13)
  - Volunteer (Box 13)
  - Junta for Progressive Action (Box 13)
  - HRA-annual report, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Youth-Urban Service Corps (Box 13)
- Labor
  - Labor (Box 13)
  - Labor relations regarding correspondence, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Depart of Labor-Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA) (Box 13)
  - Labor (Box 13)
  - Department of Labor-John Romanow (Box 13)
  - Labor leaders (Box 13)
  - Labor relations (Box 13)
  - Labor relations (Box 13)
  - Labor contracts (1) (Box 13)
  - Labor contracts (2) (Box 13)
  - Labor insurance (Box 13)
  - Labor-Intergovernmental Personnel Act (IPA) (Box 13)
  - Labor, Department of-Unemployement (Box 13)
  - Labor, Department of General Correspondence (Box 13)
  - Labor pensions (Box 13)
  - Labor commissioner-Peter A. Reilly (Box 13)
  - Labor relations (Box 13)
- Library
  - Librarian (Box 13)
  - Library-Board of Directors (Box 13)
  - Library-central planning (Box 13)
  - Library-director (Box 13)
  - Library (Box 13)
  - Library, New Haven Public (1) (Box 13)
  - Library, New Haven Public (2) (Box 13)
- Mayor
  - Mayor (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Committee for the Handicapped (Box 14)
  - Mayor's-Car #1 (Box 14)
  - Mayor's-Executive Orders (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Task Force on the Arts (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Management (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Education (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Education (3) (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Education (?) (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Education (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Task Force-Education (Box 14)
  - Mayor's Task Force on Volunteers (Box 14)
  - Mayor-platform people (Box 14)
  - Mayor-reception (Box 14)
  - Mayor-advisory committee (Box 14)
  - Mayor-Fair Employment Implementation Committee (Box 14)
  - Mayor-Redistricting Committee (Box 14)
  - Neighborhood Corporations (Box 14)
  - Neighborhood Corporations (Box 14)
  - City point, concerned citizens (Box 14)
  - Dixwell Comm. (Box 14)
  - Corporations-Dixwell Neighborhood (Box 14)
  - Dwight Corporation (Box 14)
  - East Rock Association (Box 14)
  - Edgewood (Box 14)
  - Fair Haven (Box 14)
  - Hill (Box 14)
  - Legion Avenue (Box 14)
  - Lovell Community Center (Box 14)
  - Newhallville Medical Health (Box 14)